Guide to the Harry George Stutz papers, 1915-1954.
Stutz, Harry George papers, 1915-1954
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Harry George Stutz papers, 1915-1954.
2607
Harry George Stutz 1885-1954.
.4 cubic ft.
Correspondence, photographs, clippings
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, awards and citations, photos of Stutz and other JOURNAL staff members, and newspaper clippings. Includes letters and telegrams from Frank E. Gannett praising Stutz' work and commenting on the 1920 election campaigns of Warren G. Harding, James Cox, and Alfred E. Smith, Gannett's own possible gubernatorial candidacy in New York State (1936), and other aspects of State, national, and world events; letters concerning JOURNAL editorial and articles and matters of local interest from Howard E. Babcock, Neal Dow Becker, Frank D. Boynton, Maurice C. Burritt, Anna Botsford Comstock, Hollis E. Dann, Edmund Ezra Day, Edward R. Eastman, Felix Frankfurter, Othon Guerlac, Robert J. Kane, Claude L. Kulp, Harry H. Love, Deane W. Malott, Veranus A. Moore, William I. Myers, Cuthbert Pound, Ruby Green Smith, James Sullivan, Frank Thilly, Robert E. Treman, Robert H. Treman, Hendrik Willem van Loon, and others; and letters from John Fr. Moakley and others concerning Stutz' selection as a member of the Gannett Foundation.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Editor of the ITHACA JOURNAL.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, awards and citations, photos of Stutz and other JOURNAL staff members, and newspaper clippings. Includes letters and telegrams from Frank E. Gannett praising Stutz' work and commenting on the 1920 election campaigns of Warren G. Harding, James Cox, and Alfred E. Smith, Gannett's own possible gubernatorial candidacy in New York State (1936), and other aspects of State, national, and world events; letters concerning JOURNAL editorial and articles and matters of local interest from Howard E. Babcock, Neal Dow Becker, Frank D. Boynton, Maurice C. Burritt, Anna Botsford Comstock, Hollis E. Dann, Edmund Ezra Day, Edward R. Eastman, Felix Frankfurter, Othon Guerlac, Robert J. Kane, Claude L. Kulp, Harry H. Love, Deane W. Malott, Veranus A. Moore, William I. Myers, Cuthbert Pound, Ruby Green Smith, James Sullivan, Frank Thilly, Robert E. Treman, Robert H. Treman, Hendrik Willem van Loon, and others; and letters from John Fr. Moakley and others concerning Stutz' selection as a member of the Gannett Foundation.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Stutz, Harry George,1885-1954.; Babcock, Howard Edward, 1889-1950.; Becker, Neal Dow.; Berry, Romeyn, 1881-1957.; Boynton, Frank David.; Burritt, Maurice Chase, 1883-1959.; Comstock, Anna Botsford, 1854-1930.; Cox, James M. (James Middleton), 1870-1957.; Dann, Hollis, 1861-1939.; Day, Edmund Ezra, 1883-1951.; Frankfurter, Felix, 1882-1965.; Gannett, Frank E. (Frank Ernest), 1876-1957.; Guerlac, Othon Goepp, 1870-1933.; Harding, Warren G. (Warren Gamaliel), 1865-1923.; Kane, Robert J.; Kulp, Claude Livingston, 1894-1969.; Love, Harry H.(Harry Houser), 1880-1966.; Malott, Deane W. (Deane Waldo), 1898-; Moore, Veranus A. (Veranus Alva), 1859-1931.; Myers, William Irving, 1891-1976.; Pound, Cuthbert Winfred, 1864-1935.; Smith, Alfred Emanuel, 1873-1944.; Smith, Ruby Green, 1878-; Sullivan, James, 1873-1931.; Thilly, Frank, 1865-1934.; Treman, Robert E.(Robert Elias), 1888-1953.; Treman, Robert Henry, 1858-1937.; Van Loon, Hendrik Willem, 1882-1944.; Gannett Foundation.
Titles:
Ithaca journal.
Subjects:
Journalism--New York (State)--Ithaca.; Newspaper publishing--New York (State)--Ithaca.; Journalists.
Places:
New York (State)--Politics and government.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Correspondence
  - Nellie G. (Mrs. E. M.) Bansham, Secretary Tompkins County Woman Suffrage Party, Nov. 10, 1917
  - James Sullivan, 1873-, State Historian, Nov. 15, 1920
  - note from Christian M. S. Midjo, Dec. 23, 1929 P.M.
  - Jared T. Newman to F. E. Gannett (copy), June 21, 1932
  - F. E. Gannett's reply (copy), June 23, 1932
  - J. T. Newman to F. E. Bannett (copy), June 29, 1932
  - J. T. Newman, June 10, 1935
  - J. T. Newman, July 2, 1935
  - H. H. Whetzel [also earlier letter(s)], Nov. 28, 1934
  - James E. Rice, Jan. 4, 1935
    Note on reverse of picture postcard aerial view of his Egg and Apple Farm, Trumansburg, NY
  - E. R. Eastman, Apr. 11, 1935
  - copy of F. E. Gannett's reply, Apr. 15, 1935
  - E. R. Eastman, Nov. 24, 1942
  - E. R. Eastman, n.d.
  - Louis P. Smith, Vice President of Ithaca Gun Company, and Ithaca Mayor, Apr. 30, 1918
  - Louis P. Smith, Vice President of Ithaca Gun Company, and Ithaca Mayor, Dec. 23, 1935
  - Mrs. R. C. (Agda) Osborn, chairman, Civilian War Services, Ithaca-Tompkins County War Council, Jan. 31, 1944
  - Mrs. R. C. (Agda) Osborn, chairman, Civilian War Services, Ithaca-Tompkins County War Council, June 5, 1944
  - Hendrik W. van Loon, n.d.